<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name> Mod Config Menu - Impure (BETA)</name>
    <directory>mod config menu</directory>
    <id>3701683951</id>
    <description>Mod Config Menu Impure is an updated version of the Mod Config Menu mod for Afterbirth+ by the original author which retains integral features such as the ability to embed it in other mods and removes some uneeded scripts. Compatibility with old mods or mods made for unofficial versions of Mod Config Menu is kept as best as possible.

The mod has been updated to work with Repentance and Repentance+ while keeping Afterbirth+ compatibility.

The Mod Config Menu is a new menu that enables other mods to provide a simple and easy way for the player to configure them.

This mod does not do much on its own, to get into the real action you should download a mod which supports this menu.


[h1]Contributors (Thanks!)[/h1]
- Piber (me!)
- Chifilly (continued)
- kittenchilly (rep hud func)
- laceous (kcolor alpha and dpad fixes)
- Buurazu (additional ab+ compat)
- sawalk (font quality)
- Ba-koD (currentfocus getter)


[h1]My mods dont work![/h1]
- Make sure you have the latest version of mod config menu, visible in the mod config menu category
- Restart the game!

If you still have issues even after doing all this, please create an issue in the github repo: https://github.com/piber20/Mod-Config-Menu-Impure


[h1]Navigation[/h1]

Keyboard:
- Use the arrow keys or WASD keys to navigate the menu.
- Esc, backspace, or Q can be used to go back.
- E, space, or enter can be used to select an item.
- By default you can open the menu by pressing L.
- F10 will also always open the menu, this cannot be changed.

Controller:
- Both control sticks can be used to navigate the menu.
- Press B to go back.
- Press A to select an item.
- By default you can open the menu by pressing down the right control stick.


Love what I do?
[url=http://paypal.me/pibergames]Donate to me on PayPal[/url], [url=https://ko-fi.com/piber20]or tip me on Ko-fi[/url]!

Enjoy my mods?
I have a discord server! discord.gg/DbYcutKuHV</description>
    <version>1.3</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
</metadata>
